但是我可以清楚明白地告诉你们
but I could've told you from three blocks away
签下新客户  不管大小
that signing new business... no matter what the size...
才是你们的当务之急
is of the essence.
不仅仅因为你们的代理额锐减了50%
Not only because your billings have shrunk by 50%,
而是因为再过不久  你们就会被外界认为是
but because there's not much time before you'll be perceived
停滞不前了
as stagnant...
甚至  是在衰退
Worse, decaying.
听着  博士  我们都很清楚公司目前的困难之处
Listen, doctor, we know there's a black spot on the X-ray.
[doctor  双关  请他来拯救公司状况的  也可以翻作医生]
你也不必一直戳我们的痛处吧
You don't have to keep tapping your finger on it.
我建议你们做你们最擅长做的广告
I recommend that you do what you do best...
香烟广告  你们了解联邦贸易委员会的规矩
Cigarettes. You understand the F.T.C.
也深知卫生局的行事风格
You understand the surgeon general.
你们有现成的团队
You have a team in place